<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources><string name="AV.Advanced_Defence.Title">Fortgeschrittene Verteidigung</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Defence.00.Title">Fortgeschrittene Verteidigung</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Defence.01.Paragraph">Wir müssen mächtigere Verteidigungen für unsere Basis errichten um gegen die steigende Bedrohung standzuhalten</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Logistics.Title">Fortgeschrittene Logistik</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Logistics.00.Title">Fortgeschrittene Logistik</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Logistics.01.Paragraph">Unsere Ressourcenförderung zu otimieren benötigt ein Skalpell, keinen Hammer (Hammer sind ein eigenständiges Upgrade, versteht sich).</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Logistics.02.Paragraph">Diese Forschung fokussiert auf Verbesserungen von Lagerung, Sortierung und Basis-Erweiterungswerkzeuge.</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Miner_Upgrades.Title">Fortgeschrittene Ressourcenförderung</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Miner_Upgrades.00.Title">Fortgeschrittene Ressourcenförderung</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Miner_Upgrades.01.Paragraph">Diese Forschung untersucht die weitere Verbesserungsmöglichkeiten für Erzförderer und Schmelzen. Zusätzlich wird die Forschung auch am Erzbrecher voran getrieben.</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Power_Grid.Title">Fortgeschrittenes Energienetz</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Power_Grid.00.Title">Fortgeschrittenes Energienetz</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">Die kürzlich neu entdeckten Ressourcen sollten uns es möglich machen unsere Energie Infrastruktur weiter zu verbessern.</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Research.Title">Fortgeschrittene Forschung</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Research.00.Title">Fortgeschrittene Forschung</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Research.01.Paragraph">Unsere Forschungsmöglichkeiten sind limitiert durch die technischen Begrenzungen der Forschungsstation. Ein Labor könnte uns dabei helfen komplexere Probleme zu erforschen.</string>
<string name="AV.Aesthetics.Title">Ästhetik</string>
<string name="AV.Aesthetics.00.Title">Ästhetik</string>
<string name="AV.Aesthetics.01.Paragraph">Falls wir mal eine Auszeit haben (woran ich nicht glaube), haben wir immerhin die Möglichkeit unsere Basis zu verschönern. Mit farbigen Lagerkisten, Leinwänden...</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.Title">Basenbau Automatisierung</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.00.Title">Basenbau Automatisierung</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.01.Paragraph">Große Rohstoffförderungssysteme zu bauen ist die Aufgabe von Maschinen, nicht von Menschen!</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.02.Paragraph">Dieses weitreichende Projekt wird Maschinen entwickeln, die Schächte graben und automatisch bauen, neben der Verbesserung der bereits vorhandenen Möglichkeiten die Basis zu durchqueren.</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.03.Paragraph">Des weiteren wird dieses Projekt einen Sprengstoff entwickeln, der große Bereiche leer räumen kann.</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Defence.Title">Basenverteidigung</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Defence.00.Title">Basenverteidigung</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Defence.01.Paragraph">Aus deinen Forschungsergebnissen zu lokalen Lebensformen ist dir klar geworden, dass die Verteidigung der Basis eine hohe Priorität hat.</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Defence.02.Paragraph">We shall have to bring FREEDOM to this planet!</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.Title">Bergbau I</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.00.Title">Bergbau I</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.01.Paragraph">Wir müssen einen Weg finden die Rate zu erhöhen, mit der Erze abgebaut und verarbeitet werden kann. Diese Forschung wird uns hoffentlich die nötigen Ergebnisse liefern.</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_II.Title">Bergbau II</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_II.00.Title">Bergbau II</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_II.01.Paragraph">Following on from our previous research on mining upgrades we should be able to further improve our drill motor and forced induction upgrades.</string>
<string name="AV.Black_Box_Data.Title">Black Box Data</string>
<string name="AV.Black_Box_Data.00.Title">Black Box Data</string>
<string name="AV.Black_Box_Data.01.Paragraph">Your suit contains a black box that stored all sensor readings leading up to your crash on the planet. Researching this data could help you determine what exactly happened.</string>
<string name="AV.Improved_Ore_Scanning.Title">Improved Ore Scanning</string>
<string name="AV.Improved_Ore_Scanning.00.Title">Improved Ore Scanning</string>
<string name="AV.Improved_Ore_Scanning.01.Paragraph">We have encountered a problem in our search for resources to expand our base!</string>
<string name="AV.Improved_Ore_Scanning.02.Paragraph">Our ore scanner is configured for locating unknown materials for research and classification. Its ability to find new sources of specific known materials is limited. It should be possible to use a small quantity of spare ore to act as an advanced filter allowing us to locate just the resources we require.</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_I.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades I</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_I.00.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades I</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_I.01.Paragraph">It is time to begin research on how to replicate the advanced capabilities of the Ore Smelter supplied with our Central Power Hub. The basic smelters we have been able to construct are too slow and are wasting precious resources.</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_II.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades II</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_II.00.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades II</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_II.01.Paragraph">It should be possible to further enhance the capabilities of the ore extractor. This project will also investigate alternative methods of collecting ore.</string>
<string name="AV.Local_Life_Forms.Title">Local Life Forms</string>
<string name="AV.Local_Life_Forms.00.Title">Local Life Forms</string>
<string name="AV.Local_Life_Forms.01.Paragraph">This planet is not dead! Scanners are detecting both plant and animal life forms. This project will investigate the life forms and determine whether they present a threat.</string>
<string name="AV.Power_Grid.Title">Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Power_Grid.00.Title">Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">We cannot survive on just the power produced by our Central Power Hub for long. As our base expands we'll need to find new ways to generate power and transfer it to distant mining operations so that we don't need to run about powering them manually.</string>
<string name="AV.Suit_Upgrading.Title">Suit Upgrading</string>
<string name="AV.Suit_Upgrading.00.Title">Suit Upgrading</string>
<string name="AV.Suit_Upgrading.01.Paragraph">Your environmental suit is the most advanced piece of exploration engineering known to man. Unfortunately its utility depends upon a modular upgrade system currently beyond our manufacturing capabilities. It is time to look into how you can create your own upgrades away from the factories back home. You can use a bit of help surviving in this harsh environment.</string>
<string name="AV.Ultimate_Power_Grid.Title">Ultimate Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Ultimate_Power_Grid.00.Title">Ultimate Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Ultimate_Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">Following on from our success with the MK4 power storage system we should be able to design the ultimate power storage device.</string>
<string name="AV.Ultra-Power_Grid.Title">Ultra-Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Ultra-Power_Grid.00.Title">Ultra-Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Ultra-Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">We have reached the limits of power we can store in a single 1m cube. This project will investigate the feasibility of bigger power storage devices.</string>
<string name="AV.Upgraded_Power_Grid.Title">Upgraded Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Upgraded_Power_Grid.00.Title">Upgraded Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Upgraded_Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">Our power infrastructure is coming along nicely. Our battery technology is quite limited though, this project will attempt to design a better battery which can store more power providing us a bigger buffer.</string>
</resources>
