<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources><string name="CO.Advanced_Defence.Title">Advanced Defence</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Defence.00.Title">Advanced Defence</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Defence.01.Paragraph">We have successfully designed a missile turrets and make further improvements to the energy turret. We will need to manufacture missiles and this will require a supply of fuel!</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Logistics.Title">Advanced Logistics</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Logistics.00.Title">Advanced Logistics</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Logistics.01.Paragraph">We now have a new mass storage system and a sorting mechanism for moving ore between conveyor belts.</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Miner_Upgrades.Title">Advanced Miner Upgrades</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Miner_Upgrades.00.Title">Advanced Miner Upgrades</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Miner_Upgrades.01.Paragraph">Further improvements to the ore extractor and smelter are now available. In addition we have finally perfected the Quarry system. Use the Geological Surveyor to identify a prime location then place the quarry to begin mining operations.</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Power_Grid.Title">Advanced Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Power_Grid.00.Title">Advanced Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">We have made further improvements to our power infrastructure including a new Power Storage Block and Laser Energy Transmitter.</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Power_Grid.02.Paragraph">We also have some provisional designs for a new type of Power Generator, however to complete this research we will also need to find a denser source of energy than the coal we have been relying on so far.</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Research.Title">Advanced Research</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Research.00.Title">Advanced Research</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Research.01.Paragraph">We now have a design for a research laboratory and the assembly machines required to supply it with experimentation pods.</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Research.02.Paragraph">The laboratory is required for researching advanced projects which improve your technology level unlocking new projects and recipies. A total of 27 laboratory components are required (manufactured in 3 stacks of 9 components each) and must be built in a 3 by 3 by 3 configuration.</string>
<string name="CO.Advanced_Research.03.Paragraph">For more information on using the laboratory please refer the following guide:</string>
<string name="CO.Aesthetics.Title">Aesthetics</string>
<string name="CO.Aesthetics.00.Title">Aesthetics</string>
<string name="CO.Aesthetics.01.Paragraph">In the unlikely event we have some down time we can prettify our base with a variety of coloured storage crates and canvas.</string>
<string name="CO.Base_Building_Automation.Title">Base Building Automation</string>
<string name="CO.Base_Building_Automation.00.Title">Base Building Automation</string>
<string name="CO.Base_Building_Automation.01.Paragraph">We now have a wide variety of new machines available for automating our base. Use the Macerator to grind up useless rock in exchange for the occasional useful ore. The auto-excavator can dig out shafts above it while the auto-builder can construct long conveyor runs for us.</string>
<string name="CO.Base_Building_Automation.02.Paragraph">Use the lifts to safely travel between your surface base and deeper mines. Use the explosives to clear out large areas or destroy hostile targets.</string>
<string name="CO.Base_Defence.Title">Base Defence</string>
<string name="CO.Base_Defence.00.Title">Base Defence</string>
<string name="CO.Base_Defence.01.Paragraph">We can now bring FREEDOM to this planet!</string>
<string name="CO.Base_Defence.02.Paragraph">Our base defence research has been successful, we now have three turrets available for manufacture. The ARTHER turret is power efficient and has a long range, but must be operated by ARTHER so we should position it carefully to protect our resource infrastructure while we gather the materials required to build and power the standalone turrets.</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.Title">Basic Mining Upgrades I</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.00.Title">Basic Mining Upgrades I</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.01.Paragraph">We have successfully researched a number of upgrades to improve our resource collection capability.</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.02.Header">Basic Ore Smelter</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.03.Paragraph">We can now construct a basic ore smelter. This does not support any upgrades and is slower and less efficient than the regular smelter supplied with the outpost pod but it should help eliminate that bottleneck for now.</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.04.Paragraph">Most of the resources we have found near the surface are not well suited for constructing ore smelters, however scans have shown some small rock formations which may have the properties required.</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.05.Header">Forced Induction</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.06.Paragraph">Forced induction modules can be placed on top of regular smelters to improve the smelting rate at the cost of more power. The basic smelter doesn't support these.</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.07.Header">Drill Motors</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.08.Paragraph">Drill motors can be inserted into an ore extractor to improve their extraction speed at the cost of more power.</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_II.Title">Basic Miner Upgrades II</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_II.00.Title">Basic Mining Upgrades II</string>
<string name="CO.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_II.01.Paragraph">Further improvements for our ore extractors and smelters are now available.</string>
<string name="CO.Black_Box_Data.Title">Black Box Data</string>
<string name="CO.Black_Box_Data.00.Title">Black Box Data</string>
<string name="CO.Black_Box_Data.01.Paragraph">A thorough analysis of the black box data recorded by your suit has now been completed. It confirms your visual analysis that a foreign object, believed to be a meteor, hit the station as you were preparing to dock. The resulting explosion damaged your ship's manoeuvring thrusters causing a crash landing on this alien plant. No other survivors have been detected at this time.</string>
<string name="CO.Black_Box_Data.02.Paragraph">It is not known why the meteor remained undetected by the stations long range scanners, possible causes include a system fault or sabotage.</string>
<string name="CO.Black_Box_Data.03.Paragraph">In a fortunate turn of events an outpost construction pod survived the explosion and locked on to your ship's distress signal. It has landed next to the crash site. It is a standard Vortox X103 MK V pod containing a Central Power Hub surrounded by an Ore Smelter, Manufacturing Plant and Research Station. It has also come equipped with an Autonomous Robotic Defense System which should help us to survive any early attacks should we find any hostile life on this planet.</string>
<string name="CO.Frozen_Factory.Title">The Frozen Factory!</string>
<string name="CO.Frozen_Factory.00.Title">Local Life Forms</string>
<string name="CO.Frozen_Factory.01.Paragraph">TNow this research is completed, we can progress onto build the Cold Cavern Climate Control Centre (CCCCC or C5 for short!). We\'ll need to build this machine in the Cold Cavern, feed it power, and then it should just simply, slowly, convert the cavern into a wonderful balmy area, where we can setup properly and await rescue.</string>
<string name="CO.Frozen_Factory.02.Paragraph">This new machine is significantly more advanced (and fragile!) than the old CPH - we should be able to design, research and build much larger, faster and more complicated mining and resource machines. First of all, we're going to need some more advanced materials, and for this, we'll need a special machine to deal with the super-hardened ores.</string>
<string name="CO.Frozen_Factory.03.Paragraph">If we construct the Hard Rock Grinder on a suitable 3x3 piece of Chromium and Molybdenum, we should be able to construct a new type of drill. Nano-disintegrators will be ideal for making the flat surface needed.</string>
<string name="CO.Improved_Ore_Scanning.Title">Improved Ore Scanning</string>
<string name="CO.Improved_Ore_Scanning.00.Title">Improved Ore Scanning</string>
<string name="CO.Improved_Ore_Scanning.01.Paragraph">We have successfully upgraded the ore scanner to support filtering. To do this create a blank ore ping at the manufacturing plant then convert it into the required ore ping filter using your suit's self crafting capability (C).</string>
<string name="CO.Improved_Ore_Scanning.02.Paragraph">Place the ore ping filter into your hotbar, select it, then activate (LMB). This will feed it into the ore scanner and a filtered ping will be dispatched by the ore scanner. The filter is consumed.</string>
<string name="CO.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_I.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades I</string>
<string name="CO.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_I.00.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades I</string>
<string name="CO.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_I.01.Paragraph">We have successfully designed a new Ore Smelter. This will require some advanced materials not found near the surface.</string>
<string name="CO.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_II.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades II</string>
<string name="CO.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_II.00.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades II</string>
<string name="CO.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_II.01.Paragraph">Further upgrades to the ore extractor are now available. We have also researched a new Geological Surveyor which can be used to identify locations rich in ore deposits. We should identify some prime locations while we continue research on a new Quarry system.</string>
<string name="CO.Local_Life_Forms.Title">Local Life Forms</string>
<string name="CO.Local_Life_Forms.00.Title">Local Life Forms</string>
<string name="CO.Local_Life_Forms.01.Paragraph">This planet appears to contain a variety of plant and animal life, not all of it friendly.</string>
<string name="CO.Local_Life_Forms.02.Paragraph">Scanners are detecting a number of flying lifeforms nearby which pose a potential risk. Designs for a Threat Scanner are available to monitor their progress. We should also investigate setting up some base defenses. Potentially more concerning we have detected a number of large organic structures underground which could interfere with our efforts to secure a reliably supply of resources.</string>
<string name="CO.Power_Grid.Title">Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Power_Grid.00.Title">Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">We now have a new method of generating and transporting power. This project has also designed new upgrades for ARTHER and a new machine, the Matter Mover, capable of teleporting materials from one storage hopper to another.</string>
<string name="CO.Power_Grid.02.Header">Pyrothermic Generator</string>
<string name="CO.Power_Grid.03.Paragraph">This machine will convert combustible resources in an attached storage hopper into power. It requires a lot of fresh air so loses efficiency with depth.</string>
<string name="CO.Power_Grid.04.Header">Laser Energy Transmitter</string>
<string name="CO.Power_Grid.05.Paragraph">Place next to a power generator or battery to transmit power up to 64m to a battery, power comsumer or another Laser Energy Transmitter. We can use this to send power to our deeper mining operations.</string>
<string name="CO.Suit_Upgrading.Title">Suit Upgrading</string>
<string name="CO.Suit_Upgrading.00.Title">Suit Upgrading</string>
<string name="CO.Suit_Upgrading.01.Paragraph">With some minor adjustments, it should be possible to produce suit upgrades from basic machinery design, miniaturised to be wearable. The most obvious upgrades are a better solar cell and cold insulation to operate at higher efficiency on this hostile planet. You're going to need to use a Hydrojet Cutter upgrade on your Manufacturing Plant for this!</string>
<string name="CO.Suit_Upgrading.02.Paragraph">To use a suit upgrade simply craft one and keep it in your inventory.</string>
<string name="CO.Ultimate_Power_Grid.Title">Ultimate Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Ultimate_Power_Grid.00.Title">Ultimate Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Ultimate_Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">Success! The biggest power storage device we could ever need is now within our manufacturing capabilities. As an added bonus we have also designed a better solar panel which we can place directly on top of our large structures such as the laboratory, MK4 and new MK5 batteries.</string>
<string name="CO.Ultra-Power_Grid.Title">Ultra-Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Ultra-Power_Grid.00.Title">Ultra-Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Ultra-Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">We have finished designs for a massive battery capable of storing a vast amount of power.</string>
<string name="CO.Upgraded_Power_Grid.Title">Upgraded Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Upgraded_Power_Grid.00.Title">Upgraded Power Grid</string>
<string name="CO.Upgraded_Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">We have developed a new battery capable of carrying a much bigger charge. We also have designs for a more power Laser Energy Transmitter, however this requires materials with more advanced properties than those found near the surface.</string>
<string name="CO.Upgraded_Power_Grid.02.Paragraph">It is likely that we will be able to make further improvements to our energy storage and transmission, however we will need to perform research on more advanced materials before we will be able to do this.</string>
</resources>
