<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><resources><string name="AV.Advanced_Defence.Title">Advanced Defence</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Defence.00.Title">Advanced Defence</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Defence.01.Paragraph">We need to build more powerful base defenses to take down the bigger threats!</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Logistics.Title">Advanced Logistics</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Logistics.00.Title">Advanced Logistics</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Logistics.01.Paragraph">Optimising our mining operation requires a scalpel, not a hammer. (Hammers available as a seperate upgrade, of course).</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Logistics.02.Paragraph">This research project will focus on improvements in storage, sorting and additional base construction tools.</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Miner_Upgrades.Title">Advanced Miner Upgrades</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Miner_Upgrades.00.Title">Advanced Miner Upgrades</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Miner_Upgrades.01.Paragraph">This project will investigate further improvements to the ore extractor and smelter. In addition research will continue work on the new Quarry system.</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Power_Grid.Title">Advanced Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Power_Grid.00.Title">Advanced Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">The advanced materials we have recently discovered should allow us to make further improvements to our power infrastructure.</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Research.Title">Advanced Research</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Research.00.Title">Advanced Research</string>
<string name="AV.Advanced_Research.01.Paragraph">Our research progress is being limited by the constraints of the research station. We need to design a new laboratory to continue with more advanced projects!</string>
<string name="AV.Aesthetics.Title">Aesthetics</string>
<string name="AV.Aesthetics.00.Title">Aesthetics</string>
<string name="AV.Aesthetics.01.Paragraph">In the unlikely event we have some down time we can prettify our base with a variety of coloured storage crates and canvas.</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.Title">Base Building Automation</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.00.Title">Base Building Automation</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.01.Paragraph">Building a huge mining operation is a job for machines, not man!</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.02.Paragraph">This wide-ranging project will design machines for automated excavation and construction in addition to improving the options available for traversing your base.</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Building_Automation.03.Paragraph">In addition to automatic excavation this project will seek to produce an explosive which can be used the clear out a large area.</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Defence.Title">Base Defence</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Defence.00.Title">Base Defence</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Defence.01.Paragraph">Following on from your research into the local life forms it is clear that defensive systems must be a high priority.</string>
<string name="AV.Base_Defence.02.Paragraph">We shall have to bring FREEDOM to this planet!</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.Title">Basic Mining Upgrades I</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.00.Title">Basic Mining Upgrades I</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_I.01.Paragraph">We need to improve the rate at which we can improve the rate at which we can collect and smelt ore. This project will focus on improving the performance of ore exractors and smelters.</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_II.Title">Basic Miner Upgrades II</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_II.00.Title">Basic Mining Upgrades II</string>
<string name="AV.Basic_Mining_Upgrades_II.01.Paragraph">Following on from our previous research on mining upgrades we should be able to further improve our drill motor and forced induction upgrades.</string>
<string name="AV.Black_Box_Data.Title">Black Box Data</string>
<string name="AV.Black_Box_Data.00.Title">Black Box Data</string>
<string name="AV.Black_Box_Data.01.Paragraph">Your suit contains a black box that stored all sensor readings leading up to your crash on the planet. Researching this data could help you determine what exactly happened.</string>
<string name="AV.Improved_Ore_Scanning.Title">Improved Ore Scanning</string>
<string name="AV.Improved_Ore_Scanning.00.Title">Improved Ore Scanning</string>
<string name="AV.Improved_Ore_Scanning.01.Paragraph">We have encountered a problem in our search for resources to expand our base!</string>
<string name="AV.Improved_Ore_Scanning.02.Paragraph">Our ore scanner is configured for locating unknown materials for research and classification. Its ability to find new sources of specific known materials is limited. It should be possible to use a small quantity of spare ore to act as an advanced filter allowing us to locate just the resources we require.</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_I.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades I</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_I.00.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades I</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_I.01.Paragraph">It is time to begin research on how to replicate the advanced capabilities of the Ore Smelter supplied with our Central Power Hub. The basic smelters we have been able to construct are too slow and are wasting precious resources.</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_II.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades II</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_II.00.Title">Intermediate Miner Upgrades II</string>
<string name="AV.Intermediate_Miner_Upgrades_II.01.Paragraph">It should be possible to further enhance the capabilities of the ore extractor. This project will also investigate alternative methods of collecting ore.</string>
<string name="AV.Local_Life_Forms.Title">Local Life Forms</string>
<string name="AV.Local_Life_Forms.00.Title">Local Life Forms</string>
<string name="AV.Local_Life_Forms.01.Paragraph">This planet is not dead! Scanners are detecting both plant and animal life forms. This project will investigate the life forms and determine whether they present a threat.</string>
<string name="AV.Power_Grid.Title">Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Power_Grid.00.Title">Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">We cannot survive on just the power produced by our Central Power Hub for long. As our base expands we&apos;ll need to find new ways to generate power and transfer it to distant mining operations so that we don&apos;t need to run about powering them manually.</string>
<string name="AV.Suit_Upgrading.Title">Suit Upgrading</string>
<string name="AV.Suit_Upgrading.00.Title">Suit Upgrading</string>
<string name="AV.Suit_Upgrading.01.Paragraph">Your environmental suit is the most advanced piece of exploration engineering known to man. Unfortunately its utility depends upon a modular upgrade system currently beyond our manufacturing capabilities. It is time to look into how you can create your own upgrades away from the factories back home. You can use a bit of help surviving in this harsh environment.</string>
<string name="AV.Ultimate_Power_Grid.Title">Ultimate Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Ultimate_Power_Grid.00.Title">Ultimate Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Ultimate_Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">Following on from our success with the MK4 power storage system we should be able to design the ultimate power storage device.</string>
<string name="AV.Ultra-Power_Grid.Title">Ultra-Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Ultra-Power_Grid.00.Title">Ultra-Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Ultra-Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">We have reached the limits of power we can store in a single 1m cube. This project will investigate the feasibility of bigger power storage devices.</string>
<string name="AV.Upgraded_Power_Grid.Title">Upgraded Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Upgraded_Power_Grid.00.Title">Upgraded Power Grid</string>
<string name="AV.Upgraded_Power_Grid.01.Paragraph">Our power infrastructure is coming along nicely. Our battery technology is quite limited though, this project will attempt to design a better battery which can store more power providing us a bigger buffer.</string>
</resources>
